On 15th August, we went to Muniya's school to
eat laddus and when our turn came, the
laddus were finished.  So friends, today is
15th August, Bharat Mata ki
Jai.   That's
why Munia was ready wearing the fairy dress
and was asking me to drop her to school.
But just now Papa had plucked ladyfinger from the field,
which Mummy washes with water
and asks me to hold the sack.  He said
that father will go to sell it.  Rest of the
friends, we also found some crooked ladyfingers
which we gave to Aunty Tuntun to eat,
changed our dress and made Munia sit on the bike. We went to
a shop and she was
saying, brother, please put a tricolour sticker on my cheek,
we were about to put it on, when suddenly a
Gandhiji rally of her school
comes, in which Munia also joins, after visiting the
rally she goes back to her school.
I also went to his school and then took
out my drone and started taking drone view of the school.  He
said that Principal Sir will get
me extra laddus.  But I
felt bad when the flag was hoisted here
and everyone got laddus.  But when our turn
came, the laddus were finished.  It was good
that the brother who distributed it was my subscriber and
he brought the laddu again and gave it to me.